Finding Aid for the The Sigaux Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Actors - Joë Bousquet. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Actors - Pierre Boutang. Press clipping. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Actors - Philippe Bouvard. Journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Actors - Emmanuel Bove. G. S. notes, book advertisement poster (for E. Bove's Armand, inscribed to G. S. with additional writing on the back). (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Actors - René Boylesve. Journal excerpt, book advertisement pamphlet, typed and bound manuscript (Le Premier Amour: René Boylesve et Louise Renault par Gerard-Gailly. Tour-Descartes, 1972, "Groupe Loches-Descartes des Amis de René Boylesve" - numbered copy, # 3 of 125). (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Actors - Pierre-Paul Bracco. Press clipping. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Charles Braibant. Journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Robert Brasillach. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Fernand Brandel (loose item). Journal/book excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Louis Branquier. Journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Henri Brémond. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Jean-Claude Brisville (loose item). Press clipping. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Vincent Brion. Press clippings. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Jacques Brosse. Press clippings. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Jean Bruce. Press clippings. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - R. P. Bruckberger (Le Réverend Père Bruckberger / Raymond-Léopold Bruckberger). Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Brummel (George / Georges Brummel). Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - J. B. Brunius (Jacques-Bernard Brunius). Press clipping. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Ferdinand Brunot. Journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Edmond Buchet. Press clippings. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Buffon (le Seigneur de Montbard / Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de Buffon). Journal excerpt. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - Bussy Rabutin (Roger de Rabutin, comte de Bussy). Press clipping. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Actors - François Buloz, 1804-1877 (loose item). Periodical (Etudes Renaniennes Bulletin, No.37 - 3e trimestre 1978). (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Généralités - Émile Augier. Journal and book excerpts, book advertisement page, printed biographical and bibliographical notecards. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Théodore Barrière, 1825-1877. Book excerpt, press clipping, G. S. notes/manuscript (Tome 36 Génies: "Les Faux Bonshommes"). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Henry Bataille. Press clippings, book and journal excerpts, G. S. notes, book catalog page, small book (Le Théâtre Après La Guerre, by Henry Bataille, Librairie Ollendorf, Paris, 1918). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Béranger (Pierre Jean de Béranger). Journal excerpt, book catalog page. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Émile Bergerat. Book excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Henry Bernstein. Journal excerpts, press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Lucien Besnard. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Alexandre Bisson, 1848-1912 (& André Bisson ?). Correspondence (to G. S. from Gérard Baby). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - J. R. Bloch (Jean-Richard Bloch). Book advertisement pages, press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Robert Boissy. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Joseph Bouchardy. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Paul Bourget. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Anicet Bourgeois. Press clipping, program. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Eugène Brieux. Printed biographical and bibliographical notecards, journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - René Bruyez, 1886-1969. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Alfred Capus. Typed manuscript ("Au Théâtre avec Alfred Capus"), G. S. notes, journal excerpt, press clipping, book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Cham. Book excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Eugène Chavette. G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Clairville (Louis-Francois Nicolaïe). Journal excerpt (with an illustration/portrait). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - François Coppée. Journal excerpts, book excerpt, periodical (Les Premières Illustrées - "Severo Torelli: Notes et Croquis" {includes hand colored illustrations}). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Francis de Croisset. Journal excerpts (inlcuding a photocopy), periodical (La Petite Illustration, No 364 - Théâtre: no 197, 7 Janvier 1928). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - François de Curel. Journal excerpt, printed biographical and bibliographical notecards, book (François de Curel: Son Oeuvre by Paul Blanchart. Éditions de La Nouvelle Revue Critique, Paris, 1924 - "Portrait et Autographe, Document Pour l'Histoire de la Littérature Française"). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Casimir Delavigne. Photocopy of a typed manuscript/article ("Notice sur les Vepres Siciliennes"). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Albert Depit. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Abraham Dreyfus. Journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Henri Duvernois. Book excerpt, press clipping, journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Duvert et Lauzanne (Félix Auguste Duvert et Augustin-Théodore de Lauzanne de Vaux Roussel). Typed manuscript (essay/article), G. S. notes, notes in a different hand, book excerpt). (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Généralités - Adolphe D'Ennery, 1811-1899. Journal and book excerpts, G. S. notes, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Erckmann Chatrian. Book and journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Émile Fabre, 1869-1955. Press clippings journal excerpt, typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - René Fauchois. Press clippings, periodicals (Monjoie, Revue mensuelle, "Rédacteur Unique: René Fauchois". Issues: 1er Année (1933) nos. 2, and 6-12; 2e Année no. 16 (avril 1934)). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Paul Ferrier. Periodical (La Petite Illustration: Roman-Théâtre, No. 30 - 20 Septembre 1913 Série-Théâtre - No. 17). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Octave Feuillet. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Edmond Fleg, 1874-1963. Typed transcripts (2, radio), press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Robert de Flers, G. A. de Caillavet (Gaston Arman de Caillavet). Press clippings, book/journal excerpt {Internal folder: Robert de Flers, 1872-1927. Journal excerpts, press clippings}. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Frédéric Gaillardet, 1808-1882. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Simon Gantillon. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Paul Geraldy. Journal excerpts, press clippings, newsletter/typed transcript excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Henri Ghéon. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Régis Gignoux. Playtext (journal excerpt-?: "Le Monde Renversé, comédie en un acte"). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Edmond Gondinet. Journal and book excerpts (including and photocopy), small photo (by "Boyer Paris"). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Edmond Harancourt. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Maurice Hennequin. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Paul Hervieu. Journal and book excerpts (including portrait illustration), correspondence (from Paul Hervieu, 3 items total), printed biographical and bibliographical notecards, invitation (to the unveiling of a memorial plaque in honor of Paul Hervieu). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Gabriel d'Hervilliez. Playtext/journal excerpt ("Argent de Suite!, comédie en un acte et trois journées". (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Alfred Jarry. Press clippings, journal excerpts, invitation (to G. S., to attend the première production of 2 Jarry plays at the Théâtre Kaléidoscope), typed manuscript with corrections (article). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Jules Laforgue. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Lambert-Thiboust. G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Lamartine (Alphonse de Lamartine) (loose item). Typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Armand Lanoux (also: Pierre MacOrlan and Antonin Artaud) (loose item). Correspondence (to G. S. from Paule Thévenin). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Henri Lavedan (Henry Lavedan). Journal excerpt, auction catalog excerpt, booklet (Scadale Académique: Lettre à M. Henry Lavedan by G. Roncevaux. Paris, Société Libre d'Édition des Gens de Lettres, 1899). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Népomucène Lemercier. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Gaston Leroux, Théâtre. Book advertisement excerpt, G. S. notes, journal excerpt, periodicals (L'Illustration Théâtrale: No. 52, 2 Mars 1907; 8e Année - 208, 23 Mars 1912; 8e Année - 220, 24 Août 1912). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Eugène Leterrier. 2 photocopies of a list of E. Leterrier's plays and their première information. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Marie Lénéry. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Maeterlinck (Maurice Maeterlinck). Press clipping, book excerpt (photocopy). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Maurice Magre. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Jules Mary. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Meilhac et Halévy (Henri Meilhac et Ludovic Halévy). Journal and book excerpts (including a photocopy), press clippings, typed manuscript (article). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Yves Mirande, 1875-1957. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Jules Moinaux. Journal excerpts, typed book catalog excerpt, press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Paul Morand. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - André Mouézy-Eon, 1880-1967. Journal excerpts, press clipping, correspondence (to G. S. from A. Mouézy-Eon), typed manuscript (article). (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Généralités - Édouard Pailleron. Book advertisement page, journal and book excerpts, G. S. notes, press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Steve Passeur. Press clippings, G. S. notes, journal excerpts, programs. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Charles Péguy. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Jean-Victor Pellerin. Calling card ("carte de visite"), press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - René Peter, 1908-1947. Notes in a different hand (a list of première productions). (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - L. B. Picard, 1769-1828 (Louis-Benoît Picard). Book excerpt (photocopy). (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Ponsard. Book excerpt, G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Maurice Pottecher. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Xavier Privas. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Paul Raynal. Journal excerpts, typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Douanier Rousseau. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Pierre Scize. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Jean Schlumberger. Press clippings, typed transcript (radio), journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Scribe (Eugène Scribe). G. S. notes, press clippings, program, periodical (l'Amateur: Revue Belge d'Art Dramatique, Second semestre 1960. -II -III, Numéros 80-81). (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Edmond Sée. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Eugène Sue (loose item). Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Jules Supervielle. Press clippings, book advertisement page, journal excerpts, typed transcripts (2, radio). (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Georges G.-Toudouze. Journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Auguste Vacquerie. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Paul Vandenberghe. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Pierre Veber. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Villiers de L'Isle Adam. Press clippings, book advertisement excerpt, typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Waffland, 1787-1827 ({Alexis} Jacques-Marie Waffland). Notes in a different hand. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Simone Weil. Journal excerpt, press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Albert Willemetz. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Maurice Yvain, 1891-1965. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Miguel Zamacoïs. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Généralités - Bernard Zimmer. Book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Actors - José Cabanis. Typed transcript (radio), press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Martine Cadieu. Journal excerpt, press clippings (including a photocopy), book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Roger Caillois. Press clippings, journal excerpts, typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Albéric Cahnet (loose item). Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Julien Cain. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Henri Calet. Journal excerpts, book advertisement page, press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Pierre Cami. Journal excerpt, typed manuscript (article), press clipping, G. S. notes, correspondence (5 letters from Jeanne / Jeannette Cami). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Albert Caraco. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Francis Carco. Press clippings, journal excerpts, G. S. notes, book advertisement pamphlet, book catalog page, typed transcript (radio), 2 photocopies of a bibliography. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Jérôme Carcopino. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Leonora Carrington. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Michel Carrouges. Journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Casamayor. Press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Michel del Castillo. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Henry Castillou. Typed manuscript (G. S. preface), handwritten manuscript (G. S. preface), press clipping, correspondence (to G. S. from Henry Castillou). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Jean Cau. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Louis Cazamian. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Henry Céard. Press clipping, periodical (Les Hommes d'Aujourd'hui: Henry Céard, 8e volume, No 382). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Flora Cès. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Gilbert Cesbron. Book advertisement pages, book excerpts (one is inscribed to G. S. from G. Cesbron), printed bibliographical notecards/check out cards, press clippings, journal excerpt, typed biography (on stationary from "Éditions Robert Laffont"), G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Philippe Chabaneix. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Jacques Chabannes. Book dust jacket (for: Le Poison Sous la Crinoline), journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Marc Chadourne. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Louis Chaigne. Photocopy of a memo (to Emmanuel Fradkin from Louisette Grimm of Édito-Service S. A.). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Actors - Champfort (Sébastien-Roch Nicolas, dit Champfort). Printed biographical and bibliographical notecards. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Champfleury. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Maurice Chapelan. Book advertisement page, G. S. notes, press clipping, journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Paul Chaponnière. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Maurice Chappaz. Press clippings book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - René Char. Journal excerpt, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Jacques Chardonne. Pamphlet (Association Jacques Chardonne), press clippings, book advertisement/catalog excerpt, book and journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Edmonde Charles-Roux. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Philarète Chasles. Journal/book excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Robert Chasles. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - André Chastel. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Jacques Chastenet. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - André Chaumeix. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Siméon Chaumier. Journal excerpt (inscribed to G. S. by Étienne Cluzel). (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Maurice Chavardès. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Andrée Chédid. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - André Chénier. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Jacques Chenvière. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Jacques Chessex. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Gabriel Chevallier, 1895. Book advantage pages, press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - André Chevrillon. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Abbé de Choisy. Book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Christophe (Georges Colomb). Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - C. A. Cingria (Charles Albert Cingria). Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Cioran (Émile M. Cioran). Printed biographical notecard, press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Héléne Cixous. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - G. E. Clancier (Georges-Emmanuel Clancier). Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Gustave Claudin. Book excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Bernard Clavel. Press clippings, journal excerpts, book advertisement pages. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Georges Clemenceau. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Emile Clermont. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Actors - Louis Codet. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Albert Cohen. Press clippings, journal excerpts, book advertisement page. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - M. E. Coindreau (Maurice Coindreau). Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Claudine Colletet. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Georges Couchon. Press clipping, typed manuscript (photocopy - article by Guy Le Clec'h). (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Benjamin Constant. Typed transcript (radio), journal and book excerpts (including photocopies), press clippings, book catalog and advertisement pages/excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - François Coppée. Journal and book excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Tristan Corbière. Book and journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Albert Cossery. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Paul-Louis Courier. Book catalog page, press clipping (photocopy), journal excerpts (one is inscribed to G. S. by Robert Baschet), flyer (Société des Amis de Paul-Louis Courier), G. S. notes, correspondence (1. a letter from Jean Guillon of the Société des Amis de P.-L. Courier, 2. a bulletin and reservation from). (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Pierre Courtade. Press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - J. A. Coulangheon. Typed biography and bibliography. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Crébillon Fils (Claude-Prosper Jolyot de Crébillon). Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Benjamin Crémieux. Book advertisement page, press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Jeanne Cressanges. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - René Crevel. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Jacques Croisé. Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Charles et Henry Cros. Book advertisement page, journal excerpt, auction catalog pages. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Nancy Cunard, 1896-1965. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Curnonsky (Maurice Saillant). Journal excerpt. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Jean Cuttat. Press clipping. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Actors - Cyrano de Bergerac. Book advertisement pages, journal and book excerpts. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- F - Gén F-General (F = Fiction?). Press clippings, G. S. notes, notes in a different hand, book advertisement pages, book and journal excerpts, newsletters (Preuves Informations, Le Nouveau Cercle), periodicals, documents and correspondence relating to a conference of the "Fondation Royaumont", flyer ("Qu'est-ce que le Collège de 'Pataphysique?"), brochure ("Le Pavillion Henri-IV, Saint-Germain-en-Laye", printed in the 1920s), typed list with background information for several litterary prizes and their recipients, typed transcript (radio), typed book catalog (Librarie Les Pas-Perdus). (Box 31, Folder 1)
- F - 1 Individual Folders (people: Lucien Fabre to Henri Fluchère). G. S. notes, press clippings, book advertisement pages, book and journal excerpt, typed transcripts (radio), newsletter (Preuves Informations), periodical. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- F - 2 Individual Folders (people: Maurice Fombeure to Stanilas Fumet), typed transcripts (radio), book advertisement pages, press clippings, journal excerpts, typed manuscript with notes (brief biography of Max-Pol Foudret), G. S. notes, personal correspondence (letter from G. S. to ?, returned with corrections), letter (from Jean Fougère?). (Box 31, Folder 3)
- G - 1 Individual Folders (people: Emile Gaborian to Louis Gillet), press clippings, journal excerpts, correspondence (from Jean-Paul Colin), G. S. notes, periodicals, typed transcripts (radio), book catalog and advertisement pages, typed transcript of press reviews (of Antoine Giacometti's Le Figuier Maudit), book excerpt (with inscription to G. S. from Geneviève Gennari). (Box 31, Folder 4)
- G - 2 Individual Folders (people: Edmond Gilliard to Roger Grenier), book advertisement pages, typed bibliography of Jean Grenier, press clippings, journal excerpts, G. S. notes, typed manuscript (an introduction to Etienne Gilson's Saint-Thomas d'Aquin 1930, Gabalda), typed transcripts (radio), notification of T.V. premier (La Guepe). (Box 31, Folder 5)
- G - 3 Individual Folders (people: Léon Groc to Gyp), photocopy of typed transcript (of speech or article of Jean Guitton), book and journal excerpts, press clippings, book catalog and advertisement pages, typed transcript (article), typed transcripts (radio), G. S. notes, typed manuscript (preface to Jeanne la mince et L'Amour). (Box 31, Folder 6)
- E-F-G Com Individual folders (people: Simon Eine to Henri Guisol ), press cilppings, journal excerpts, calling card (Edwige Feuillère), typed transcript (radio). (Box 31, Folder 7)
- H-I-J-K Com Individual folders (people: Bernard Haller to Ursula Kubler), press clippings, a typed chronology of cinematic and theatrical roles with handwritten notes (Harry-Krimer), journal excerpts, typed transcript (radio), programs (including: les Frères Jacques). (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Com - D.E. Individual folders (people: Ira Aldridge to Charlotte Wiehe), press clippings, book and journal excerpts (including one photocopy), typed script with handwritten notes, typed transcript (radio), book catalog and advertisement pages, G. S. notes, periodical. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Com - D.F. A-B Individual folders (people: Elisabeth Alain to Raymond Brussières), press clippings (including photocopies), book and journal excerpts, playbill, typed transcript (radio), G. S. notes, typed manuscripts, book catalog pages. (Box 32, Folder 2)